Contact

tojumikie@live.com

www.linkedin.com/in/toju-mikie-87ba96101 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Electronics Repair Java Python 3

Languages

English (Native or Bilingual)

Certifications

Cloud Native Development Explorer
Oracle Cloud Infrastructure
Foundations 2021 Associate
Master the Coding Interview
AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner
Master the Mainframe 2020 - Level 3

Toju Mikie

Trainee at Cognixia

Atlanta, Georgia, United States

Summary

I have 9 years of experience, including as a Sortation Center Warehouse Associate, as a Trainee and as a Package Handler in industries including Apparel and Accessory Stores, Engineering, Accounting, Research, Management, and Related Services and Motor Freight Transportation and Warehousing. Most recently, I have been working as a Sortation Center Warehouse Associate at Amazon from August 2022, and also as a Trainee at Cognixia from June 2022. My skills and experiences include: Apache Webserver, Cashier, Computer Hardware, Data Mining, Database Administration, Desktop Pc, Eclipse, Electronics, Java, Javascript, Linux, Matlab, Mysql, Operating Systems, Oracle, Payroll Processing, Postgresql, Python, Raid, Servers, Software Development, Soldering, Sql, Tax Planning, Technical Support, Unix. I hold a Bachelor of Science degree in Computer Science from Georgia State University.

Experience

Amazon Sortation Center Warehouse Associate August 2022 - Present (2 months) Union City, Georgia, United States

Cognixia

Trainee

June 2022 - Present (4 months)

Atlanta, Georgia, United States

In training for Java, MySQL, NoSQL, Maven, servlets, Git, DevOps, AWS, Spring, Kafka, Product Engineering, HTML, CSS, JavaScript React

Pyramid Consulting, Inc Trainee October 2021 - March 2022 (6 months)

Alpharetta, Georgia, United States

Did training focused on Oracle Retail. In the training, learned Oracle Retail (formerly Retek Retail), including RMS (Retail Merchandising System), OCI (Oracle Cloud Infrastructure), OIC (Oracle Integration Cloud), RIB (Retail Integration Bus), Unix, Oracle SQL, PL/SQL, and a little bit of Java SE.

FedEx Ground
Package Handler
June 2020 - September 2021 (1 year 4 months)
Ellenwood, Georgia, United States

Help to put packages in trailer trucks. Occasionally scan packages as well before putting them in the truck. Also, will sometimes help with unloading, to remove packages from trucks.

Mikie's Big Burger Cashier, Prep Cook, Food Delivery, Payroll February 2020 - September 2021 (1 year 8 months) McDonough, Georgia, United States

Work at the cash register to handle orders, and also handle orders through phone calls. Also, help prepare food and get supplies, equipment, and foodstuffs for the restaurant. Help with food orders that need to be delivered as well as handling the food delivery at times. Occasionally, help with company tax needs and company payroll to ensure that it gets done in a timely manner.

Revature

Trainee

January 2020 - January 2020 (1 month)

Tampa/St. Petersburg, Florida Area

Spent 4 weeks in paid training to learn technologies and software development processes, including Agile and the software development lifecycle

RAM-Tech PC Solutions
3 years 7 months
Hardware Support Specialist
August 2019 - January 2020 (6 months)
Stockbridge, Georgia

Repaired computers and servers, provided computer and server set-up, provided customer support, went onsite to provide IT support

Information Technology Technician
July 2016 - August 2019 (3 years 2 months)
Stockbridge, Georgia

Repaired computers and servers, provided computer and server set-up, provided customer support, went onsite to provide IT support

Walmart

Electronics Sales Associate May 2016 - July 2016 (3 months) Ellenwood, Georgia

Sold electronics, including computers, tablets, phones, game consoles and games, and televisions

RAM-Tech PC Solutions Information Technology Intern August 2014 - May 2016 (1 year 10 months) Stockbridge, Georgia

Repaired computers and servers, computer and server set-up, provided customer support, went onsite to provide IT support

Education

Georgia State University

Bachelor of Science - BS, Computer Science · (2017 - 2019)

Clayton State University
Computer Science · (2014 - 2017)

Valdosta State University
Computer Science · (2013 - 2014)